<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smartphones on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/tags/smartphones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Smartphones on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Zongqing Lu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://z0ngqing.github.io/tags/smartphones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Smartphone Networks</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/mobile/</guid>
      <description>Smartphones have great networking capabilities. They can access the Internet through cellular networks or wireless access points and communicate with nearby devices using WiFi Direct or Bluetooth. However, these network functions may not work in some circumstances where cellular towers and network infrastructure are destroyed, e.g. in disaster recovery. Nevertheless, communications in such scenarios are very important, and hence, in this research, we aim to build smartphone networks to provide communications without relying on cellular networks, wireless access points, or network infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Sensing Using Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/health/</guid>
      <description>Mobile devices, such as smartphones, have become commonplace in health care settings, leading to the development of both platforms and applications for health care, e.g., HealthKit on iOS, where apps can collect users&amp;rsquo; health and activity data and the data will be used for medical research to bring more powerful health solutions. However, no data is collected for the research of infectious diseases. Moreover, currently, most health data are collected by manual input or external devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>