<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026 Zongqing Lu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Embodied Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/embodied/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/embodied/</guid>
      <description>Embodied intelligence focuses on creating robots that can perceive, reason, and act in the physical world. It brings together dexterous hand manipulation, humanoid whole-body control, and foundation models that link perception, language, and action. By combining these elements, embodied AI aims to enable robots that can generalize and perform complex real-world tasks with human-like adaptability.
Dexhand Manipulation  Dexterous hand manipulation focuses on enabling robots to interact with objects with the precision, adaptability, and coordination of human hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generalist Agents</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/agi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/agi/</guid>
      <description>Recently developed foundation models, such as large language models and multi-modal models, open great opportunities to build generally capable agents, combined with reinforcement learning. This project focuses on learning skills and foundation models and connecting them to build generalist agents. In the following, we introduce some of our studies. For more details, please refer to the papers.
Plan4MC We study building a multi-task agent in Minecraft. Without human demonstrations, solving long-horizon tasks in this open-ended environment with reinforcement learning (RL) is extremely sample inefficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rl/</guid>
      <description>Reinforcement Learning Besides MARL, we also pay attention to the fundamentals of reinforcement learning including the tradeoff between exploration and exploitation, and experience replay for off-policy RL.
GENE Sparse reward is one of the biggest challenges in RL. We propose a novel method called Generative Exploration and Exploitation (GENE) to overcome sparse reward. GENE dynamically changes the start state of agent to the generated novel state to encourage the agent to explore the environment or to the generated rewarding state to boost the agent to exploit the received reward signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/communication/</guid>
      <description>Agent Communication Biologically, communication is closely related to and probably originated from cooperation. For example, vervet monkeys can make different vocalizations to warn other members of the group about different predators. Similarly, communication can be crucially important in MARL for cooperation, especially for the scenarios where a large number of agents work in a collaborative way, such as autonomous vehicles planning, smart grid control, and multi-robot control. Communication enables agents to behave collaboratively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/cooperation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/cooperation/</guid>
      <description>Cooperation Cooperation has been one of the major research topics in MARL. We investigate multi-agent cooperation from many aspects, including adaptive learning rates, reward sharing, roles, and fairness.
FEN Fairness is essential for human society, contributing to stability and productivity. Similarly, fairness is also the key for many multi-agent systems. Taking fairness into multi-agent learning could help multi-agent systems become both efficient and stable. However, learning efficiency and fairness simultaneously is a complex, multi-objective, joint-policy optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RL/Multi-Agent RL</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/learning/</guid>
      <description>Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) has recently attracted much attention from the communities of machine learning, artificial intelligence, and multi-agent systems. As an interdisciplinary research field, there are so many unsolved problems, from cooperation to competition, from agent communication to agent modeling, from centralized learning to decentralized learning. MARL has been the main research focus of our lab. We are investigating the field from many perspectives. In the following, we introduce some of our studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RL/MARL Applications</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rlapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rlapp/</guid>
      <description>Reinforcement learning (RL) has the potential be applied to many real-world applications. In our research, we also investigate the applications of RL and Multi-agent RL. Currently, we have been investigating two applications: one is traffic signal control; another is EDA. Traffic signals coordinating traffic movements are the key for transportation efficiency. However, conventional traffic signal control that heavily relies on pre-defined rules and assumptions on traffic conditions is far from intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Video Processing Using Deep Learning on Networked Devices</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/video/</guid>
      <description>The vast adoption of mobile devices with cameras has greatly assisted in the proliferation of the creation and distribution of videos. Videos, which are a rich source of information, can be exploited for on-demand information retrieval. Deep learning using Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) is state of the art computer vision techniques that can be used for information retrieval. However, due to the high computation of video processing using CNNs, it is not feasible or costs too much to process all videos at a centralized entity, considering a large set of videos which is common in this big data epoch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Smartphone Networks</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/mobile/</guid>
      <description>Smartphones have great networking capabilities. They can access the Internet through cellular networks or wireless access points and communicate with nearby devices using WiFi Direct or Bluetooth. However, these network functions may not work in some circumstances where cellular towers and network infrastructure are destroyed, e.g. in disaster recovery. Nevertheless, communications in such scenarios are very important, and hence, in this research, we aim to build smartphone networks to provide communications without relying on cellular networks, wireless access points, or network infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Sensing Using Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/health/</guid>
      <description>Mobile devices, such as smartphones, have become commonplace in health care settings, leading to the development of both platforms and applications for health care, e.g., HealthKit on iOS, where apps can collect users&amp;rsquo; health and activity data and the data will be used for medical research to bring more powerful health solutions. However, no data is collected for the research of infectious diseases. Moreover, currently, most health data are collected by manual input or external devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Social Structure for Network Designs</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/network/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/network/</guid>
      <description>The proliferation of mobile devices, such as smartphones and tablets, and the popularity of online social networks that link humans, mobile devices and Internet together, increasingly emphasize the role of human behaviors on network designs. Due to the involvement of human behaviors, social structure provides crucial information of network structure and node organization, and thus can be exploited for network designs, e.g., in online social networks and mobile social networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>