<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reinforcement Learning on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/tags/reinforcement-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reinforcement Learning on Zongqing&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2024 Zongqing Lu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://z0ngqing.github.io/tags/reinforcement-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Generalist Agents</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/agi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/agi/</guid>
      <description>Recently developed foundation models, such as large language models and multi-modal models, open great opportunities to build generally capable agents, combined with reinforcement learning. This project focuses on learning skills and foundation models and connecting them to build generalist agents. In the following, we introduce some of our studies. For more details, please refer to the papers.
Plan4MC We study building a multi-task agent in Minecraft. Without human demonstrations, solving long-horizon tasks in this open-ended environment with reinforcement learning (RL) is extremely sample inefficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RL/Multi-Agent RL</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/learning/</guid>
      <description>Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) has recently attracted much attention from the communities of machine learning, artificial intelligence, and multi-agent systems. As an interdisciplinary research field, there are so many unsolved problems, from cooperation to competition, from agent communication to agent modeling, from centralized learning to decentralized learning. MARL has been the main research focus of our lab. We are investigating the field from many perspectives. In the following, we introduce some of our studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RL/MARL Applications</title>
      <link>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rlapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://z0ngqing.github.io/project/rlapp/</guid>
      <description>Reinforcement learning (RL) has the potential be applied to many real-world applications. In our research, we also investigate the applications of RL and Multi-agent RL. Currently, we have been investigating two applications: one is traffic signal control; another is EDA. Traffic signals coordinating traffic movements are the key for transportation efficiency. However, conventional traffic signal control that heavily relies on pre-defined rules and assumptions on traffic conditions is far from intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>